{
    "id": "813c61d4223a45529b707502e3bf76ca",
    "title": "Confusing Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "At a ………….. date, he became the CEO of the company.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0020011339e045579adcb72910fb08dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer the ………………. proposition to the former.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60dba491d3864b099d5b0686ebed6d4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have an ………………. brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4740b8d977aa419896354b95d9814bab"
        },
        {
            "question": "The niece is ……………… than her uncle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d73a39279afe443ca1540de731c35a32"
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………….. brother serves in the army.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1647848fd2d8430e9d3e5a4eb43c599c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the ……………….. member of the club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eldest",
                "oldest",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0458b5a1254543d4802e6d9b1d58eaf6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Broach is ……………… from Bombay than Surat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "caedef7228b747b8b558956f2fec5c60"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………. time I saw him he was in high spirits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "latest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a54d2c731d364ffda6523080182da4ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………… Moghul Emperor came to an ignominious end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "latest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f90b79c75494b16974aef539e2e137a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The …………….. hospital is two miles from here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nearest",
                "next"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dbf508c59e7a4c8b827139b706436dc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have a brother. He is ……………. than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "older",
                "elder"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ffcb6ccdd11a4233932ed2980f071fc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "No ………………… reasons were given.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "further",
                "farther"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5544ebc95a5e447dadf969a712eeb1c6"
        }
    ]
}